LIAM D HALL

Mobile: +44 (0) 7367 583649 Email: hall.d.liam@gmail.com
Portfolio Site: liam-hall.herokuapp.com
Github: github.com/LiamDHall

PROFILE

Experienced in graphics design in clothing manufacturing as well as direct sales and working in a customer-facing role in estate agency, leisure and licensed premises industries. Completed the Code Institute Full Stack Development course. Holds a full UK driving licence and owns a car.

EDUCATION AND ACHIEVEMENTS

Full-Stack Software Development Diploma - Code Institute: Grade Pending

April 2020 - April 2021

Please find the websites and web applications I have created at: https://github.com/LiamDHall I have gained the following skills and experience in:

Languages: Python, JavaScript JQuery, HTML, CSS including Grids and Flexbox **Frameworks:** Django, Flask **Database APIs:** MongoDB, AWS S3 **Testing:** Django TestCase, Manual Testing **Version Control:** GIT, Github

Richard Hale School September 2007 – July 2012

• GCE Qualifications: Biology - C, Chemistry - C, Mathematics - D.

Achieved the Duke of Edinburgh Bronze Award, including 6 weeks of training with the Hertford Fire & Rescue Service on breathing apparatus, RTA rescue procedures and use and care of hoses and other equipment.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

GRAPHIC DESIGNER - Rock The Dragon

March 2020 - Present

- Manually tested the new company website relaying the issues I found to the company hired to build it.
- Designed and created over 40 logos for dance schools across the UK.
- Converted over 75 logos from image format to vectors with some images only being 50px in height
- Introduced a production system / strategy that increased production by 100% (from 20-25 orders a day to 40-50). This system was more efficient and reduced bottlenecking of certern steps and simplified many processes so anyone could step in and take over the roll.
- Discussed design ideas and concepts with customers over the phone and email.
- Gained an understanding of designing whilst having to consider limitations imposed when using physical media.
- Gained professional proficiency in Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Hotfix Era.

SUPERVISOR - Cinnabar

June 2019 – February 2020

- Managed a team of up to 7 people for 11 hour shifts making sure everyone maintained focus and morale.
- Responsible for the bartenders hitting performance targets. Achieved by keeping a log of total sales per weekend shift in a leaderboard with a prize/incentive for the person at the top, at the end of each month.

COCKTAIL BARTENDER - CBK, Rotorua, New Zealand COCKTAIL BARTENDER - Scotty's, St Anton, Austria SUPERVISOR - Cinnabar COCKTAIL BARTENDER - The Snug

May 2018 - May 2019

Dec 2017 - April 2018

September 2015 – Dec 2017

March 2015 - September 2015

August 2014 - March 2015

OPERATIONS MANAGER - Solutions For Property

 Ran all of the logistics for the plumbing and maintenance services such as time, access, approval of all jobs and placing them on the system tracker to inform the engineers and work men.

LANGUAGES, SKILLS AND INTERESTS

- Code Languages: Python, JavaScript, JQuery, JSON, HTML5, CSS and CSS Variables.
- **Skills:** Django, Flask, Balsamiq, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, Smart Cuts, Cutting Master 4, Hotfix Era. Balsamiq Wireframing.

•	Interests: Freestyle sno	owboarding, Krav Ma	aga, Digital Art in F	Photoshop, Landsca	pe Painting, Roller	Skating